that job was a great job I loved that
job I had that job for a long time but
it wasn't all good days I'm gonna tell
you a story about the worst day I ever
had at that job okay now this story
begins with me odd to explain I was a
recreational therapist okay I used to
work with kids that have disabilities
and my job would be to like help them
have fun that was my whole thing it was
a really sweet gig so I'm working with
this new client okay and he lives in a
medical facility I've never been to
before all right now I would describe
this kid as having a little bit of
autism and tons of cerebral palsy okay I
would describe him as like Paul's to the
walls all right so much palsy all right
it's so much it's okay he's not here and
no he has a great sense of humor so I'm
there with him I meet him he's there
with this nurse okay and I'm like hey
what do you want to do today he's like I
want to play video games and I'm like
you got it buddy so we're gonna play
video games I'm meeting this kid and
it's nurse it's like hey I have an
emergency my shift is over I got to go
the next nurse will be here in like 15
minutes don't worry about it and I'm
like hey probably don't leave me alone
with this kid I'm not like qualified to
take care of him and she's like don't
worry the next nurse will be here so she
leaves me with him we're hanging out
playing video games everything's going
fine okay you know everything's going
well it's like 30 minutes this nurses in
here yet another 30 minutes she hasn't
shown up but I'm like what is going on
and then he's like hey I'm getting
really hungry like well I don't live
here I don't know where food is I got
Doritos in my bag you want to share some
Doritos he goes yeah man this sounds
great so we're eating Doritos playing
video games everything's going fine
about 45 minutes goes by now he starts
doing this shaking thing in his chair
and I'm like hey man what's this and he
goes oh this is my poop dance like what
what is that and why do you have it
you know what do you mean and he goes
yeah I have diarrhea how could you
possibly know that
and he goes because I'm allergic to corn
and you gave me Doritos yeah what what
why did you let me give you Doritos Ben
to which he replies because they're
delicious like all right okay
I'm fair so he's like I gotta go and I'm
like dude I'm not qualified to like take
you out of your straps and help you I'm
not like a medical professional I don't
know what to do and he's like you're
gonna help me or you're gonna watch me
poop my pants yeah he was making so much
eye contact I was like I choose the
other thing I always choose the other
thing what is the thing that's not
hugging you boobed your pants I choose
that one you know I do not want any part
of this and he's like I don't want to
help him by neetu and I'm like listen I
don't know what to do and he's like I
don't need help man
you're making it more complicated than
it needs to be all I need help with is
pulling up my pants at the end of
getting back into my chair and I was
like you can do everything yourself and
he was like yeah and I was very specific
I go you can even wipe yourself and he
was very condescending he goes yeah I
can wipe myself so I'm like alright I
guess I'll help you so I'm pushing him
around this facility trying to find a
bathroom I've never been here before I'm
like kicking down doors and people are
like hey man what's going on and I'm
like oh this kid's gonna poop and
they're like what and I'm like already
gone you know the nurses the next day
are like I guess a guy with face tattoos
kidnapped a kid I don't
someone was pooping I'm not sure what's
going on here anymore you know so I'm
pushing you around this facility trying
to find a place I push them into the
first bathroom I find and there's and we
get inside and he goes hey man there's
no railing in here and I'm like we're
looking for a bathroom not a set of
stairs oh so he's like this is the place
it doesn't matter it's happening and I'm
like okay what do you need for me and
he's like you're gonna be a railing now
and I'm like okay so I wheel him up to
the toilet and I stand either side and I
put my arm out and I'm helping him up
and I'm getting him undone so that he
can go to the bathroom and I realize I'm
pinned into the corner of the bathroom
near the toilet and I'm like oh no I
have to get around him so I start
getting around him and that's when he
has a palsy spasm and he falls into my
lap and proceeds to poop everywhere okay
there's soul mates like Lucky Charms and
Doritos and shame it's so gross it's so
so gross and I'm like no and as I'm
yelling out his head lolz back and he
sneezes into my mouth
yeah I felt some of you being like well
shame that's pretty gross but step it up
buddy come on there you go okay
yeah seeds into my mouth I'm try not to
puke at this point just hard so gross
I'm not I'm not feeling it okay and then
he looks up at me and with no irony he
goes I lied to you I'm gonna need help
wiping yeah so that was my worst day at
work
you